同志们 这是我办过最棒的一次洗衣派对了
Guys,this is the best laundry party I've ever thrown.
不是所有词后面加上"派对" 都能变得很欢乐
You can't just stick the word "party" on anything and make it fun.
你不爽是因为错过了Brad的牙龈手术派对
You're just mad because you missed Brad's gum surgery party.
下周我要去颗痣 留点时间
Well,save the date,because next week... I'm having an asymmetrical mole removed.
派对主题是"康复凯旋"
The theme will either be "dressed to the benigns"
或者"安排后事"
or "it's time to get my affairs in order."
你要洗的衣服还真不少
Ooh! That's a lot of laundry,buddy.
这都是要来的
Actually,this is all candy.
我一路玩着"不给就捣乱"过来的
Yeah. I trick-or-treated my way over here.
离万圣节还早着呢
It's not even close to Halloween.
可事实证明只要按别人家门铃
Yeah,but it turns out if you ring someone's doorbell
冲着他们使劲吼"不给就捣乱"
and then scream in their face "trick or treat?" as loud as you can,
你要什么他们都给你
they'll just give you whatever they have on them.
这家伙把他要洗的衣服都塞给我了
This one guy-- he gave me all his laundry.
最棒的是全都是特大号的
And the cool is that it's all XXL,
所以我再胖点还能穿
so I have room to grow into it.
你真是个奇葩
You're a terrifying individual.
Dave 衬衣要跟我的一起洗吗
Oh,hey,Dave,you wanna throw your shirts in with mine?
不不 我这几件需要特殊对待
Oh,no,no,no. These-- these require special attention.
我都穿在身上跑动晾干
In fact,sometimes I throw them on wet
好让衣服不变形
and run-dry them so they keep their shape.
然后我出了一身汗 又得重新洗
But then I get all sweaty,and it's like,here we go again!
不管怎样 要做自己
Would not change a thing about what you're doing.
- 谢谢你 - 老天
- Thank you. - Oh,my God.
水族馆有个团购 跟海豚游泳
There's a groupon at the aquarium to swim with the dolphins.
- 老娘超爱海豚 - 别
- Mama likes dolphins. - Nope.
你总这样
Mama always does this.
看见喜欢的就买 转身就没兴趣了
You see something you like,you buy it, and then you lose interest immediately.
- 你太冲动了 - 我才没有冲动
- You're too impulsive. - I am not too impulsive.
你在坦帕订了限时度假屋
You bought us a time-share in Tampa.
中介说那是东部的萨克拉门托
The lady at the kiosk said it's the Sacramento of the East.
现在每年都要去坦帕了
Now we gotta go to Tampa every year.
去Tampa不是旅游 是养老
Tampa's not a place that you go. It's a place that you end up.
- 我家这位也这样 - 咋啦
- My bitch is the same way. - What?
Brad在购物台买了好多垃圾 我们自己都能开个节目卖了
Brad buys so much junk on QVC,we could start our own show.
不过不行
But we won't.
不管你说什么 Jane 那可不是垃圾
Whatever,Jane. It's not junk, all right?
比如 你们这些小猪洗衣服的时候
For example,while you porkers have been doing laundry,
我却坐在这里 锻炼腹肌
I've been sitting here,getting a killer ab workout
用我新买的腹肌带
with my new... electro ab-belt.
在电动脉冲刺激下...
The electro-pulse stimulation...
重塑你的...腹肌!
Tones and shapes your ...abs!
给塑形新的...定义!
For improved muscle defi...nition!
话说回来...
Anyway...
我预测Alex团购了也不会用
I predict that Alex buys the groupon and never uses it.
我绝对会用的
I am absolutely gonna use it.
好吧 你囤了多少团购券
Okay,how many unredeemed groupons do you have currently?
什么
What?
- 多少 - 11个
- How many? - 11.
11个 我觉得你该吸取教训了
11. Okay. Well,I think it's time that you learned a lesson.
这样吧 如果你一周内用完所有团购券
Tell you what. If you use all your groupons in one week,
我就送你海豚的团购 还跟你一起去
I'll buy you that dolphin groupon and... I'll do it with ya.
一言为定
You're on,ping-pong.
好的
Mm. Okay.
祝你好运 Alex 我支...持你
Well good luck,Alex. I'm rooting for you.
你还好吗
Okay? You all right?
我想说的是
What I meant to say is,
我挺...你!
I'm in your...corner!
天哪
Oh,God!
它...不停顿了
It's just-- it's not even pulsing anymore.
- 快脱下来 - 一直电击
- Get that off of him. - It's just constant.
- 痛死我了! - 电到我了!
- So painful! - It shocked me!
- 弄下来! - 我在弄 开关在哪
- Take it off! - All right. I'm trying. I don't know where the--
我得垫个垃圾袋坐
I need to sit on a trash bag.
- 垃圾袋 需要... - 别
- We need a trash bag. We just-- it happened. - No!
常有的事 没关系
It's happens. It just happens. It's okay. It's okay.
<font color=#70DB93>-=伊甸园美剧 http://bbs.sfile2012.com=- -=伊甸园字幕站 http://ytet.org/=- 荣誉出品 本字幕仅供学习交流 严禁用于商业途径</font>
<font color=#70DB93>-=http://bbs.sfile2012.com=- -=http://ytet.org=-  Proudly Presents</font>
<font color=#70DB93>-=YTET-伊甸园字幕组=- 翻译: 力士 睡睡 Iphigenie 校对: Jasmine在腐国深感抱歉 时间轴:有志青年</font>
<font color=#70DB93>-=http://bbs.sfile2012.com=- -=http://ytet.org=-  Sync:有志青年</font>
<font color=#70DB93>幸福终点站 第3季 第21集</font>
<font color=#70DB93>Happy.Endings S3Ep21</font>
上次我把仿麂皮外套落在那了
Last time I was there,I think I left a suede jacket.
我想找回来 不管猫还在不在里面
I'd love to get that back,with or without the cat.
对了 我在衣服里养了只猫
Oh,PS. There's a live cat living in that jacket.
天哪
Oh,my God.
我看见那个被我毁一生 所以要毁我一生的男人
I see the guy whose life I ruined, who in turn vowed to ruin mine.
要是找到我的外套猫 叫它外套猫
If you find my coat cat,he answers to the name "coat cat."
要挂了 拜!
Gotta go. Bye!
嗨 Chase
Hey,Chase.
哥们 知道什么最酷吗
Buddy,old pal. You know what's cool?
上次我们见面时 一切都好的不能再好了
The last time we saw each other, we left things on the best terms possible.
我一直在找你 Max
I've been looking for you,Max.
要告诉我你重获工作 又和妻子复合了吗
To tell me that you're back at work and that you're back with your wife?
不 多亏你 我现在还没工作
Nope. Thanks to you,I'm still unemployed,
我前妻跟我弟弟订婚了
and my ex-wife's engaged to my brother.
我想自杀 不过你猜 谁要在他们婚礼上祝酒
I'd kill myself, but guess who has to give a toast at their wedding?
天 还真是祸不单行
Ooh,boy. That is rough'em stuff'em robots,pal.
我跟踪你好几周了 想着搞个计划毁掉你的人生
I've been following you for weeks, trying to craft a plan to ruin your life.
好笑的是 你的人生已经绝顶悲催了
Funny thing is,your life is so pathetic I doubt I can make it any worse.
破坏不能
It's un-sabotagable.
别这样嘛 最近我日子过的挺好的
Hey. Come on. I got a lot of stuff going on.
我刚买了长柄勺 盛汤用
I,uh,recently bought a ladle... for soups.
我读了半篇关于鱼肝油的报道
I,uh,I read half an article on fish oil.
我刚学会海姆利克急救法
And,uh,I just learned how to do the heimlich.
对自己也行 再也不用担心嚼东西了
Can even do it on myself,so now chewing food is my prerogative.
你的人生太渣了
Your life sucks.
没有工作 没有爱情 公寓乱七八糟
You have no job,no love life. Your apartment is disgusting.
我想过放老鼠进去
I considered releasing rats in there,
但你家里的老鼠比我的还大
but you already had rats in there way bigger than mine.
别自责 兄弟
Don't beat yourself up,pal.
我们都尽力养自己的鼠
We're all just raising our rats the best we can.
告诉你 我不想再毁你人生了
What I'm trying to say is,I'm not gonna ruin your life
因为已经糟到无可复加了
because it's impossible to ruin something that's already terrible.
就好比在人人加了好几个妈做好友
It'd be like adding more moms to Facebook.
Penny 花钱请洁耳工去你家
Penny,aren't you sick of paying a professional ear cleaner
让你痛苦的去除耳垢 你就不烦吗
to come to your house and painfully remove your unwanted canal wax?
Brad 我知道Jane让你把那些玩意都卖掉
Look,Brad,I know Jane's making you sell all your little gadgets,but--
现在不用麻烦了 只要有了...新型洁耳机
Well,now you don't have to... with the revolutionary ear genie.
- 试试吧 - 不要! 什么
- Try it out. - No! What?
我才不要买你用过的洁耳机
No,I do not wanna buy your used ear cleaner.
完全理解 我懂的
Totally understand. I get it.
来聊聊鞋子吧 你都怎么加热的
Let's talk shoes. How are you heating yours?
我有麻烦了 我要帮助
I have a problem! I need help!
I have a problem and I need help.
- 不 我先 - 好了 好了
- No! Me! - Okay,okay.
Alex先说
Alex first. Alex first.
好的 谢啦
Okay. Thank you.
知道Dave约定用完团购券的事吧
So you know how Dave challenged me to do all these groupons?
我一直不在状态
I-I keep getting distracted.
今早的陶艺课就没去
I didn't even make it to my pottery class this morning.
小狗派对
It's a... puppy party!
好多的小狗狗啊
It was a total puppy pile-on.
所以你没用团购券
So you never used your pottery groupon?
- 说明你还有11个 - 12个
- Which means you still have 11. - 12.
宠物店的人说有增长睫毛的团购
The puppy store lady said that there was a groupon for eyelash extensions.
我很需要 我睫毛像我爸 又短又粗
I need those! I have my dad's stubby eyelashes.
你们要陪我一起 让我抓紧用完
You guys have to do these groupons with me, keep me on track.
作为请求救援专家
Well,as the author of several dozen cries for help,
久病成医 我知道什么请求可以救
I know a good one when I hear one.
但是公平起见
But we have to be fair.
为了公民的利益
In the interest of conducting a civil discourse,
伊利诺伊州的肥仔也聊一聊吧
the fat slob from Illinois has the floor.
谢谢 你们记得Chase吧
Thank you. Now you guys remember Chase,right?
- 记得 人超酷 发誓要毁你人生 - 就是他
- Yes. Super cool guy,vowed to ruin your life.- That's the one.
他说我的人生已经糟到极点 破坏不能
Well,he said that my life is so pathetic that it is un-sabotagable.
我要改善生活 证明他是错的
So I need to improve my life to prove him wrong.
那个 Max...
Well,Max...
我们喜欢挑战
you know we love a challenge.
可是自杀行径不属于挑战范畴
But that's not so much a challenge as it is a suicide mission.
- 我们选择帮Alex - 太棒了!
- So we're gonna go with Alex! - Yes!
不好意思 你自己看着办吧
Sorry,brah. You're on your ahn.
你不是大兵瑞恩 我也不跟Tom Hanks握手
You ain't Private Ryan, and I ain't shaking hands with Tom Hanks.
Max 只有一个人喜欢这个挑战
Max,there's only one person who's really up to this challenge.
我等你来等了10年了
I've waited ten years for you to come to me.
你从哪找到我穿内裤的照片
How did you get a picture of me in my underwear?
你一直都只穿内裤的啊
Well,you're-- you're always in your underwear.
很难找到一张你穿衣服的
In fact,it's hard to find a picture of you when you're clothed.
你要挑战的任务艰巨难当
I do not envy the task you are about to embark on.
红箭头是干什么用的
What are all those red arrows for?
那是你要改善的部位
Oh,those are all the areas that need improvements.
那就是全部了
But those are all of them.
是啊 你失败的地方挺多的
Yeah. You got lots of bad areas.
你是同性恋的下限
You're like the Oakland of gay guys.
好吧 从哪开始
Okay. Well,where do we start?
细节 比如头发 淋浴
Small stuff-- haircut,shower,
别再问服务员菜能不能做成千层面
stop asking waiters if your food could be "lasagna'd."
Jane 用你的强迫症拯救我吧
Jane,I'm in your undiagnosed OCD hands.
咱们开始吧
Let's do this.
瞧瞧谁在这
Well,well,well...
这不是怀疑的Dave么
if it isn't doubting Dave.
可能要叫怀疑的海豚人Dave了
Might have to start calling you "doubting dolphin Dave."
用掉了几张团购券很爽吧
Feeling pretty good 'cause you knocked out a few groupons,huh?
不止几张 是很多张
Not just a few. Many few.
我们买了带帽围巾
We got these cool hooded scarves...
还洁了两次牙
and we got our teeth whitened... twice.
洁牙哦
Whitened up them teeth!
我们还去画像了 给他看
And we took this gorgeous portrait. Show him.
好 是不是很美
Got it. Isn't it beautiful?
像两个拉拉领养了个苏丹失足少年
It's like a portrait of two lipstick lesbians who adopted a lost boy of Sudan.
是啊 很开心
Yeah,it's just been good times.
接下来 龙舌兰
Oh! You guys,up next... tequila shots!
团购...半价
50% off... with this guy.
好的
Si,senor.
我恨龙舌兰
I hate tequila.
团购太惨无人道了
These groupons are the worst thing ever.
最糟的是以这速度
No,the worst thing ever is that at this rate,
Alex明天就能用完这些券
Alex is gonna finish these groupons by tomorrow.
知道该怎么办么
You know what we need to do?
我们该捣乱 让她完不成
We need to sabotage her so she can't finish.
为什么
Why would I do that?
因为如果Alex赢了
Because,Pen,if Alex wins this,
她会拉你团购一辈子的
she's gonna be dragging you to groupons for the rest of your life.
你希望50岁还单身一人 去半价的高空杂技课么
You wanna be 50 years old and single and doing half-priced trapeze lessons?
不爽你假设我还单身
I resent you making me single in this hypothetical.
至少让我有尊严的守寡
See,you could've at least given me the dignity of having been widowed.
干杯
Okay! Down the hatch.
我们修眉团购10分钟后开始
Our brow-shaping groupon is in 10.
要在眼睛间打激光
They shoot a laser right between your eyeballs!
- 准备好了么 - 嗯
- Here. Ready,Pen?! - Yes!
- 咱们整垮这贱人吧 - 好
- Let's take that bitch down. - Yeah.
Jane
Jane!
来看这机器 太棒了
Check out this machine. It's amazing.
它能从地面吸走垃圾
It sucks the garbage off the ground,
现在我不用破兜装垃圾
so now I don't have to throw it out on the street
好偷着扔到马路上了
through a hole in my pocket,Andy Dufresne style.
Max 你看上去很棒
Max,you look great.
真的很棒
I mean,really great.
我感觉很好
I feel great.
早上我洁牙时牙龈只流了很多血
This morning,I flossed my mouth, and my gums only bled a lot,
而不是非常多的血
as opposed to an alarming amount.
你今天去商店面试了吧
And you had that interview today at that grocery store?
进展怎样
How did that go?
完胜
I nailed it.
超市最糟了
This supermarket is the worst.
你该这么做
Here's what you gotta do.
把甜麦片从底层移到顶层
You gotta move the sugar cereals from the bottom shelf to the top shelf,
因为我这种人不会或不能弯腰去拿
'cause people like me don't and/or can't bend over to pick it up.
你不是应征装袋工的么
I thought you were here for the bagger position?
我说了 有问题么 快说
I said,any questions?! Chop-chop!
你不是说完胜么
I thought you said you nailed it.
确实完胜啊
I did nail it,Jane.
事实上...他们让我做...
In fact... they're making me...
经理助理
assistant manager.
不可能
No way.
小菜一碟
Curds and whey.
他说喜欢我的实话和新观点
Guy said he liked my real talk and fresh takes.
计划比想象中进展快的多啊
Wow. My plan is working much faster than I thought.
仔细想想…
Come to think of it...
是不是太快了
maybe a little too fast?
我竟然很开心 乳头都不疼了
I mean,I'm weirdly happy. My nipples stopped burning.
以前没人喜欢我的实话和新想法
No one likes my real talk and fresh takes.
只有一个人喜欢
Once,a guy liked my real fresh take on talks,
那人是我 我是骗人的
and that guy was me,and I was lying.
你想说什么
What is your point?
仅凭我自己没可能改变这么大
There's no way my life could've turned around this quickly on my own.
唯一解释是Chase在偷偷改善我的生活
The only logical explanation is that Chase is secretly trying to improve it,
捧高摔重
building me up only to knock me down.
你疯了吧
That is crazy.
放松 享受过程
Just relax and enjoy your progress.
享受过程 是么
Enjoy the progress,huh?
- Chase也会这么说 - 什么
- That's exactly what Chase would say! - What?!
现身吧
Show yourself,you beautiful genius!
- Max - 让我撕碎这张皮
- Max! - I'll tear this face off!
够了
All righty.
Max 我不是Chase
Max,I'm not Chase!
我错了
My bad,Jane.
- 实话说 - 嗯
- Full disclosh, though? - Yeah?
这不是第一次觉得你是汉子了
Not the first time I thought you were a dude.
谢谢
Thank you.
今天是Alex海豚团购的最后期限
Okay. Today is the last day that Alex's dolphin groupon is available.
- 我们要让她不能用完剩下的券 - 对
- All we have to do is make sure she doesn't finish the others.- Exactly.
你 Alex和Brad
So you,Alex,and Brad are supposed to go to dinner tonight
要去新的烧烤店晚餐
at that new barbecue joint,
但是不用去了 因为我俩要
except you're not because you and I are gonna--
用手机砸窗户
Throw the phones through the window,
让菜盘里全是碎玻璃和手机
covering their pulled pork with shattered glass and phones.
什么 我们要打电话定很多位
What? No. No,we're gonna call and make so many reservations
让你们去不成
that you guys can't get in.
你忘了很重要的一点
But you are overlooking one very obvious detail--
餐馆会记下我们电话号的
the restaurant is gonna recognize our number.
所以我弄了这些一次性的
That's why I got all these burners,baby.
来砸订餐员 干扰他
To throw at the reservation guy to distract him. Yes!
不不不 蠢货
No! No! You fool,no!
我们从40个不同的身份和手机打电话
We call from 40 different phones using 40 different personas.
这是你的
Here are yours.
南方律师
Uh,Southern lawyer?
"我确认"
"I do declare."
楠塔基特岛家庭主妇
Nantucket housewife.
"来杯白葡萄酒"
"Uh,white wine spritzer,please?"
Julian Assange 维基泄密那家伙么
Julian Assange? Is that the Wikileaks guy?
- 我演不了他 - 要我演他么
- I can't do him. - You want me to do him?
随便 把握角色的精髓
Whatever. Just honor the spirit of the characters.
但也要好好玩哦
But don't forget to have fun out there,okay?
你的第一个角色是Alex
Now your first character is Alex.
以她名义打电话给餐厅 取消订位
Call the restaurant as her and cancel the reservation.
- 我不知道能不能行 - 你可以的
- Oh,I don't know if I can do this. - You got this. You got this.
我是Alex Kerkovich
Hey,I'm Alex Kerkovich.
我很矮而且我喜欢排骨
I'm short and I love ribs.
你了解Alex和订位流程么
Do you know anything about Alex or how reservations work?
她听起来就这样
This is what she sounds like!
我要取消预订
I need to cancel a reservation.
太好了 谢谢
fantastic. Thank you.
惨了
We're screwed.
她已经去了 而且把三张排骨团购都用了
She has been there already and used all three ribs groupons herself.
我忘了排骨是她早餐最爱
God,we should've known. Breakfast ribs are her favorite.
完了完了完了
Damn,damn,damn!
你干嘛这么急 不过一个赌而已
Wait. Why do you care so much? I... it's just a bet.
因为我关心Alex
Because I care about Alex,
我要让她成熟点 负责任地用钱
and I'm trying to help her grow up and be more responsible with her money.
真正原因是什么
What's the real reason?
我对海豚有种偏执的恐惧
I have a paralyzing fear of dolphins--
我一接近它们
as in,when I'm near them...
就大便失禁
I lose my poop.
拜托 现在只剩一张团购券了
Now come on. There's only one groupon left,
是在健身营的军事障碍课
and it's the military obstacle course at the Major Fitness Boot Camp.
如果她用了 我就输了
If she does this,I lose,all right?
- 所以我们必须阻止她 - 好
- So we gotta stop her. - Okay.
为什么怕海豚 它们那么无害
Why dolphins? They seem so sweet.
它们懂的很多
Let's just say they understand a lot of things,
但偏偏不懂“不”的意思
but "no" isn't one of them.
Max
Hey, Max.
- 新工作怎样 - 很好
- How's the new job? - Great.
太好了
Actually,too great.
我信用卡今早申到了 牙也不疼了
This morning,I got approved for a credit card, my teeth stopped burning.
Chase肯定做了什么
There's no way Chase is not behind all this.
这都是每天发生的平常事
Max,that is just normal stuff that happens to pretty much everyone every day.
天 她噎着了
Oh,my God. She's choking!
Kevin 该怎么办
Kevin! I don't know what to do!
什么都非我不可么
Do I have to do everything?!
准备好了么 来了
Okay,ready? Here we go.
Heimlich急救法 数到三 一 二 三
Heimlich on three. One,two,three!
好吧
All right.
- 太好了 - 不好
- It's great! - No,it's not.
Chase知道我在学急救术
Chase knows that I've been learning CPR.
他是这一切的幕后推手
He is behind everything that's happening.
这只是个巧合
It's a coincidence.
非常感谢
Thank you so much.
我是芝加哥WLS的记者
I'm a reporter for WLS Chicago,
你一定要让我做个关于你的报道
and you've gotta let me do a story about you.
你是个真正的英雄
You're a real hero.
- 嗯 一定是Chase - 对 是Chase
- Yeah,it's Chase. - Yeah,it's Chase.
欢迎来到少校健身训练营
Welcome to the Major Fitness Boot Camp!
我们有一张军事障碍课的团购券
We have a groupon to use the military obstacle course.
迫不及待啊 上吧
Yep. Can't wait. Let's do this.
抱歉 这儿关闭了
Sorry,it's closed!
场地被水淹了 极其恶心 女士
The course is flooded. It's super yucky,ma'am.
好吧 那我们要克服的障碍就只剩失望了
Welp,I guess the only obstacle left for us to overcome is disappointment.
就这样了? 我输了?
That's it? I lose?
抱歉
I'm sorry!
你什么话都非要用吼的么
Do you have to yell everything?
我吼是因为受了伤
I'm yelling on account of my injury!
怪不得 在战斗中听力受损
Of course. You lost your hearing in combat.
感谢你为维护自由做出的牺牲
Well,we appreciate the sacrifice you've made to preserve our freedom.
不
No!
我用了电视购物的洁耳机 把耳膜弄破了
I busted my eardrums using that ear genie ear wax remover you buy on TV!
别用玩意儿
Stay away from them!
好啦
Well,well,well.
Penny说你没完成障碍课程
Penny told me you didn't finish the obstacle course.
看来跟海豚在水族缸游泳的时间
So it looks like instead of swimming in a tank with dolphins,
我只好用来泡在咱的浴缸里 读那本没劲的"时间旅行者的妻子"了
I'll be soaking in our tub with a well-worn copy of "The Time Traveler's Wife."
对 你赢了 我输了
Yeah,you won. I lost.
你说得对 我总是做错误的决定
You're right. I make terrible decisions.
我是个冲动的傻瓜
I'm an impulsive idiot.
没有啦 我觉得不至于是傻瓜
Oh,honey,come on. I wouldn't say "idiot."
真的? 我回家路上买的这台棉花糖机
Really? The cotton candy maker I bought on the way home
可能不同意这点
might disagree with you.
它不能说话 那种要贵200刀
It doesn't actually talk. Those were,like,$200 more.
别太苛求自己了
Hey,listen. Don't beat yourself up over it.
我也喜欢棉花糖
I love cotton candy,too.
我准备把它退了
Well,I am returning it,
因为我该拨开迷云
'cause it's time for me to get my head out of the clouds
也不能吃像云一样的东西了
and stop eating food that looks like clouds.
花椰菜就挺健康 也像云朵啊
Cauliflower is healthy,and it looks like clouds.
这下我糊涂了 而且饿了
Now I'm confused... and hungry.
想不想来点美味蓬松的棉花糖?
Would you care for some delicious, fluffy cotton candy?
我撒谎了 我多花了200刀
I lied. I did spend the extra $200.
实际是300刀
And it was... $300.
Chase做得太漂亮了
Chase is doing some dang old good work.
向他脱帽致敬
A tip of the ol' James hat to him.
但我不会让他享受摧毁我的快感的
But I am not gonna give him the satisfaction of destroying my life.
不行
No,sir.
我会自己来
I'm gonna do that myself.
- 你确定要这么做? - 嗯
- You're sure you wanna do this? - Yeah.
令我心碎 不过没问题
Breaks my heart,but okay.
你是有全职工作的吧
You do have a full-time job,right?
很好 就这样
There we go. Get it.
好了 你差不多打回原形了
Well,you're pretty much right back to where you started--
烟熏人肉
human pastrami.
还不够 Jane
It's not good enough,Jane.
你得把我整到负五级
You gotta take me to negative 5,
确保Chase永远放过我
make sure Chase stays away for good.
但再没什么好毁的了
But there's nothing left to destroy.
你只剩健康了
I mean,all you really have left is your health.
好吧 这也拿去吧 揍我
Okay. Take it. Hit me.
不 我不会揍你的
No,I'm not gonna hit you.
Jane 你的脚踝好胖
Jane,you ankles are fat.
我才不会中招呢
Yeah. I'm not falling for that.
Jane 你的戚风蛋糕湿度不对
Jane,your bundt cake is on the wrong side of moist.
胡扯
That is ridiculous.
有时你毫无准备 真是可悲啊
At times,you're woefully unprepared.
这是我第一次被个女人吸引
This is the first time I've ever been attracted to a woman.
我想让你怀上我的孩子
I wanna put a baby in you.
你们干嘛 带我来幸灾乐祸的么
So what'd you guys do,bring me here to gloat?
Alex 我要坦白一下
Alex... I have a confession to make.
我和Penny来了一出法式破坏艺术
Penny and I engaged in the French art of sabotage.
- 我们淹了场地让你上不了课 - 什么
- We flooded the course so you couldn't do it. - What?!
真不敢相信
I can't believe you guys.
我不想眼睛被激光扫
I didn't want a laser shot at my eyes.
这点无可厚非
I don't think that's an unreasonable position.
但我看见你和棉花糖机
But then,Alex,I saw you with that cotton candy machine,
我发现 我喜欢你的冲动和意气用事
and I realized that I love that you're impulsive and you do those kinds of things.
那是你的特质
That's what makes you,you.
对
Aw! Yeah,it is.
太好了 我们真互补
It's great. We really complement each other.
你是冲动的那个
I mean,you're the impulsive one,
我是踏实的那个 思路清楚
and I'm the grounded one that thinks things through.
- 不不不 - 你才不踏实
- No. No. No,no,no,no. - You're not grounded in the least.
不 不 不
No. No. No!
- 超冲动 - 对
- Super impulsive. - Yes.
我怎么就冲动了?
How am I impulsive?
你看了"慕尼黑" 就想办犹太成人礼
When you saw "Munich," you tried to get Bar Mitzvah'd.
在Alex的坦帕分时度假房隔壁 你又买了一套
You bought a time-share in Tampa next to Alex's.
你买了40个一次性手机来 做40个匿名晚餐预约
You bought 40 burner cell phones to make 40 untraceable dinner reservations.
还有脸上那堆胡子
You have the facial hair you have.
好了我承认啦
Okay,I get it! I get it.
别怪到山羊胡头上就是
Leave the goatee out of it.
- 很难做到 - 真的很难
- It's hard to leave it out. - Really hard.
还别说 也许俩冲动货也能美满在一起
You know what? Maybe two impulsive people can work in a relationship.
歌手Ice和Coco T就行
Hey,it works for Ice and Coco T.
的确是呢
Sure as hell does.
这是海豚团购券
Here's the dolphin groupon.
不过 给你之前 你得先完成障碍课程
But before I give it to you, you have to do the obstacle course.
但这里关闭了啊
But it's closed.
我们冲动一回吧
So let's be impulsive.
也许一对冲动货也有不好的一面
Perhaps there's a downside to having two impulsive people in a relationship.
应该提醒一下Ice和Coco T
Someone should warn Ice and Coco T.
我觉得你俩不能没人看着
I don't think you guys should be left alone without supervision.
就好像我们是俩30岁二货的父母
Yeah,it's like all of a sudden we're parents to two 30-year-old dum-dums.
三个
Three.
Max 再次跟你说对不起
Max,again,I am so,so sorry.
没事 你干得好
It's okay. You did good,baby.
Chase不能再伤害我们了
Chase can't hurt us anymore.
Max是你么
Max,is that you?
Chase 你怎么在这儿
Chase? What are you doing here?
我们在路上谈过后
After we spoke on the street,
我踩在你扔的一块披萨上滑倒了 还撞到了头
I slipped on that slice of pizza you dropped and I hit my head.
我都昏迷三天了
I've been unconscious for three days.
昏迷?
Unconscious?
那么不可能是你逆转我的生活 以求击溃我了
So then it couldn't have been you building my life up only to knock it down.
首先 我还好 多谢关心
First of all,I'm fine. Thanks for asking.
- 我没问 - 其次 不 我没有
- I didn't ask. - Secondly,no,I wasn't.
你在这儿正好 我想跟你说点事
But I'm so glad you're here because I wanna tell you something.
我不知道你死后会去哪
I don't know where you fall in the existence of an afterlife,
但我告诉你 还有另一个地方
but I'm here to tell you there is another place.
那是一片性灵之境 主宰者强大而仁慈
It's a spiritual realm ruled by powerful yet merciful beings.
我到过那里 Max
I was there,Max,
迈向美好永恒的宁静
and I was headed for sweet eternal peace.
可我想起来
But then I realized
我还不能飞越到更高一层
I could not transcend to the next plane
除非先把此世未竟之事了结
until I took care of the unfinished business of this world--
那就是摧毁你的生活
the unfinished business of ruining your life.
那是你
It was you.
我会回来找你的
I came back for you.
我仔细俯瞰了彼岸世界的深渊
I have looked deep into the abyss of the next world,
那十分美丽
and it is beautiful.
但开始朝圣之旅前
But before I make that pilgrimage,
我绝不会放弃破坏
I will stop at nothing to lay waste
你可悲的所谓生活
to what you so tragically call your life.
他还是那么酷
That guy is still so cool.
淡出的时间算得正好
That was perfectly timed with his exit.
他是不是先跟护士排练过
Do you think he rehearsed that with the nurses beforehand?
Max 好消息是
You know,Max,the good news is that
现在我们知道 你能够自己改善自己的生活
now we know you have the ability to improve your life all... by... yourself.
大概吧
Yeah,I guess you're right.
我很乐意帮你
And I would be more than happy to help you.
因为 只要你下定决心
Because if you put your mind to it,
你能做到原本只能梦想的事
you could achieve things you only dreamed of.
你意下如何
So what do you say?
听起来好费劲 绝对没兴趣
It sounds like a lot of work. Hard pass.
好吧 我能理解
Yeah,that's okay. I understand.
- 我得走了 保重 - 再见 各位
- Well,I gotta go,buddy. Take care. - Bye,everybody.
我升职又失败了
I got passed up for another promotion at work.
我真的需要改变一下
I really need to change some things in my life.
再想想 我干嘛要怀疑自己呢
You know,on second thought, why should I even doubt myself?
我根本就不想要那个位子
I mean,I don't even want that job anyways.
是 是
Yeah. Yeah.
Alex 你今天要跟Dave去看海豚么
So,Alex,are you going to that dolphin thing with Dave today?
糟糕
Oh,no.
我可以的 我可以的
I can do this. I can do this.
不 没门
Oh,no. No way.
我知道你们想要什么
I know what you guys want,
你们不会得逞的
and you're not gettin' it!
<font color=#70DB93>-=伊甸园美剧 http://bbs.sfile2012.com=- -=伊甸园字幕站 http://ytet.org/=- 荣誉出品 本字幕仅供学习交流 严禁用于商业途径</font>
<font color=#70DB93>-=http://bbs.sfile2012.com=- -=http://ytet.org=-  Proudly Presents</font>
<font color=#70DB93>-=YTET-伊甸园字幕组=- 翻译: 力士 睡睡 Iphigenie 校对: Jasmine腐国悔过中 时间轴:有志青年</font>
<font color=#70DB93>-=http://bbs.sfile2012.com=- -=http://ytet.org=-  Sync:有志青年</font>
<font color=#70DB93>幸福终点站 第3季 第21集</font>
<font color=#70DB93>Happy.Endings S3Ep21</font>